Godwin peter.O

Full Stack Developer

~	me@godwin.dev			E	godwin.dev	
(gpproton	in	godwin-peter		
+2348062957703						

Skills

Xamarin

Linux	
Docker	
Shell Script	
Asp.net Core	
Kubernetes	
C#	
Ansible	
Vagrant	
Node.js	
Proxmox	
Vue.js	
React.js	
PostgresSQL	
Javascript	
Laravel	
Python	
Django	
Ansible	
Angular	

Summary

A goal driven Developer / Dev-Ops Engineer with an intense passion for exploring both the technical, theoretical of software tech and an hands on experience on (Web & Mobile) application development, database, cloud platforms, virtualization, containers.

Professional Experience

drolx labs

Developer (Part-time)

2024 - present | Lagos, Nigeria

- Planning, designing and assisting in development of SaaS product
- Interacting with customers on their adapting their business processes to a requested digital workflow
- Maintaining the cloud infrastructure

Tolaram Group 🛮

DevOps Developer

2019 - 2023 Jul | Lagos, Nigeria

- Analysing existing working processes and developing mobile and web solutions
- SVN, SCRUM and container model of developing and deploying applications.
- Handling the deployment of developed applications.
- Migrating existing application to and container or cloud setup

Multipro Consumer Products Limited (BHN Division) ☑

Web Developer / Technical Manager

2017 – 2019 | Ogun, Nigeria

- Managing/ Supporting all technical tracking Technicians across west Africa.
- Review up-time for tracking devices across all regions.
- Developing/Deployment new functionalities for in-house tracking system.
- Developing custom application taking advantages of GPS tracking data.
- Management of server software and associated backup routines.

IOT Tracking - Technical Manager

2016 - 2017 | Ogun, Nigeria

- Developing/Deployment new functionalities for inhouse tracking system.
- Developing custom application taking advantages of GIS data.
- Server maintenance for Tracking system and web applications
- Technical analysis and testing of new GPS trackers.

Education

National Diploma

The Polytechnic Ibadan ☑ 2011 – 2014 | Ibadan, Nigeria

High School

Dairy Farm Senior Secondary School ☑

2007 – 2010 | Agege, Lagos, Nigeria

Courses

The Complete Xamarin Developer Course: iOS And Android! ☑

Udemy

2019

Vue.js Fast Crash Course ☑

Udemy

2019

Diploma in Web Design 🛮

Alison

2017

Interests

- Testing Opensource projects
- Coding patterns
- Home automation experiments
- Reading Japanese Manga

- Management of server software and associated backup routines.
- Updating OSM data for geo-coding server, to include map/address updates.
- Correcting Map data error on openstreet map.

Beta Bridges Limited 🛮

IT Manager

2014 - 2016 | Ikeja, Nigeria

- Maintenance of GPS tracking server platform.
- Technical analysis and testing of new GPS trackers.
- Preparing monthly performance trend report of client's tracked asset.
- Creating, updating and monitoring IT user/mail accounts.
- Performing routine audits of systems and software.
- Developing & maintaining the company IT systems, software and databases.
- Recommending and implementing improvements and efficiencies.
- Management of server software and associated backup routines.
- Maintaining documentation of changes regarding users, functions & systems.
- Managing the internal & hosted network infrastructure.
- Developing the infrastructure and systems to meet the company's needs. Design and maintenance of new and existing websites.
- Ensuring compliance with laws and regulation guiding company's IT infrastructure.

Accelerated Networks Limited

Network Technician

2013 - 2014 | Ikeja, Nigeria

- Termination of Network Cables.
- Inverter installation and maintenance.
- Conduit and surface wiring of power and data cables.
- Network troubleshooting.
- Troubleshooting and rectifying power issues.
- UPS cabling.

Projects

Trace □

A multi-purpose transportation platform

2023 Oct - present

A SaaS service that combines multiple tool required for affective logistics operation like Routing, Object tracking, meetings, trip and task schedule, shortage management, etc

References

Bharat Ramchadani, *Product Manager,* Tech Prescient bharat.ramchadani22@gmail.com, +918884416582

Fred Olowojesiku, Technical Manager, Tramigo Nigeria fred.olowojesiku@gmail.com, +2348033334635

Abiodun Agboola Solomon, MIS Manager, BHN Limited agboolas@outlook.com, +2348030776365

cash-claim 🛮

Organization expense app

2022 - 2023

An ongoing development of an expense mobile app request and approval system built with C#, Blazor and dotnet MAUI

Workshop Board

A vehicle part waiting app

2022 Jul

A PWA application for large screen or mobile that display requested vehicle parts, the technician and a timer to maintain a sense of urgency on vehicle part collection

TDMS

DMS System

2021

A vue.js /php based for an oracle custom DMS system.

MicroFrame ra

A minimal PHP framework

2020

Personally developed a PHP framework/template which specifically tuned for internal developers workflows of rapid API creation for legacy databases without necessary having in -depth knowledge of PHP's all OOP methodologies.

Proton.Frequency 🗷

A UHF RFID integration system

2019 - present

A multi device compatible free dotnet based program for UHF RFID devices

BHN Limited 2

A company single page website

2019

Redevelop a group company website in PHP and Javascript and included a customer info collection system with active notification on mail and SMS

SqlToImage

Image generator

2019

A PHP based service that generate an image report from an SQL query.

BHN Adapt - V1.0

A waybill/financial accrual system

2019 Jul – 2019 Sep

Developed and Deployed version 1 of a group company internal waybill / financial accrual system as an extension to the ERP system to enable an end to end revenue tracking.

Traccar MOD 🗆

Object tracking system

2017 – 2022 May

An object tracking system based on opensource Traccar